Recall the troops and return to court
Отдаю приказ отступаем
Yes
Слушаемся
Not long after
Вскоре после этого
Nandu City fell
пал южный город Наньду
You're still here
Ты всё ещё здесь
I've always been here
Я всегда была здесь
No matter what the outcome
Что бы ни случилось
I will face it together with Your Majesty
я буду рядом с Вашим Величеством
Great Xuan's accumulation over decades
Десятилетия накоплений великой Сюань
Now destroyed in one fire
теперь сгорели в одночасье
It is my fault
это моя вина
Since ancient times, rulers die with their state
Издревле государь умирает за свою страну
As long as I am here
Пока я жив
Great Xuan will not be humiliated
Сюань не потерпит унижения
Your Majesty still has a sword
У Вашего Величества есть меч
Has heroic spirit
дух героя
And me
и я
They say Chen and Sikong rule the realm together
Все говорили Чэнь и Сыкун правят вместе
Now
а теперь
It is Chen and Sikong
Чэнь и Сыкун
Facing survival and destruction together
вместе встретят гибель
Arm me
Наденьте на меня доспехи
Yes
Слушаемся
Miss Chen
Госпожа Чэнь
What a coincidence
Какая случайность
I am here on my granduncle's orders
по поручению дяди
To report to His Majesty
я собиралась доложить Вашему Величеству
Aren't my benefits a bit lacking?
Моя выгода не слишком ли мала
A mutually beneficial matter
Это взаимная выгода
What else does Your Highness want?
А чего ещё желает Ваше Высочество
My friendship
Дружбы моей
Does Your Highness dare to want it?
Осмелитесь ли принять её
You traitor
Продажная тварь
Look at our ancestors
взгляни на предков
Think about what you've done
подумай что ты натворила
Do you still know your surname?
хоть помнишь как тебя зовут
Chen
Моя фамилия Чэнь
This is for Your Highness
Это для Вашего Высочества
For the Chen family
для семьи Чэнь
And for the realm
и для всей Поднебесной
The best outcome
лучшее решение
Are you afraid?
Страшно
With Your Majesty here
Пока Вы со мной
I'm not afraid
не страшно
Beat the drums for me
Бейте барабаны
I will protect Great Xuan
Я защищу Сюань
Until the end
до самого конца
Corpses fill the palace
Трупы у дворца
Blood fills the streets
кровь заливает улицы
This is the integrity Xuan Kingdom lacked for decades
это честь Сюань которая запоздала на несколько десятилетий
The capital's sun
Солнце столицы
Has set
закатилось